Mustafa Abdelrahman

Berlin, Germany | mostafa.saber3789@gmail.com | (+49) 176 73803733 | msaber.dev linkedin.com/in/mustafasaber | github.com/MustafaSaber

About Me

I'm a software engineer who likes to work with infrastructure and backend systems. I have experience in building scalable and reliable systems. I mostly work/support with services making developers' life easier. Worked with GoLang, Python and Kubernetes.

Experience

Software Engineer, Zalando SE

April 2022 - Now

- Maintaining and developing Zalando's ingress controller (skipper) for Kubernetes.
- Taking part in OnCall rotation for the team.
- Working on RouteSRV, a proxy service between Skipper and Kubernetes. Helping in 3x ingress instances scaling.
- Working on implementing Kubernetes Validation Webhook for Skipper filters and predicates used in Ingress and RouteGroups resources.
- Rewriting of FabricGateway from Scala to GoLang.
- Supporting and implementing versioning for FabricGateway.

DevOps Engineer, bld.ai

April 2021 - April 2022

- Bootstrapped and automated infrastructure (CI/CD, logging, alerting and montoring) for different clients and on multiple cloud providers.
- Maintained and developed infrastructure as a code for different services.

DevOps Engineer, Tactful AI

Sep 2019 – April 2021

- Fixed ML training pipelines and improved ML infrastructure, by facilitating the deployment of ML models. Decreasing ML deployments bootstrapping from 30 minutes to 5 minutes.
- Operated and maintained the infrastructure for the company's services. Improved CI/CD pipelines and deployment strategies.
- Migrated the company's infrastructure from IBM to AWS with zero downtime.
- Trained and mentored new team members.

Education

Cairo University, BS in Computer Science GPA: 3.07/4.0

Sept 2015 - Sep 2019

Projects

GhostWriter

MustafaSaber/GhostWriter

- **My graduation project** A simple way to write and and take notes freely without the need for a special electronic pen or tablet, notes are saved as PDF in handwritten style.
- Tools Used: Intel RealSense D415/D435 Depth Camera, Python

Technologies

Languages: GoLang, Python, Bash, SQL, Java

Technologies: Kubernetes, Docker, AWS